AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
- Class photo of First primary A. 20.2 x 25.3 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref285)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo of first grade pupils with their teachers. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref286)
- Kindergarten class photo. 20.2 x 25.6 cm, 1989-1990; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref287)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Women
- Grade 11 class photo with teachers. 20.2 x 26.1 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref288)
  Adolescents; Arabic Writing; Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Class photo of Second Prep A with teachers. 20 x 24.9 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref289)
- Class photo of Second Secondary A with teachers. 20.2 x 25.6 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref290)
- Third grade school photo with teachers. 17.7 x 25.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref291)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Third grade class photo with teachers. 20.1 x 25.3 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref292)
- Third grade class photo. 20.2 x 25.2 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref293)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Fifth grade class photo. 20.2 x 25.2 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref294)
- Fifth grade class photo. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref295)
- Third Prep B Classs photo with teachers. 20 x 24.9 cm, 1999/2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref296)
- Third Prep A class photo with teachers. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref297)
- Second primary B class photo. 20.1 x 25.1 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref298)
- Second grade class photo. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref299)
- Students saluting in the school playground. 19.5 x 30.3 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref300)
  Architecture; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Uniforms
- Kindergarten class photo. 20.1 x 24.9 cm, 1999-2000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref301)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- Class photo with two teachers and a priest. 14 x 19.2 cm, 1961-1962; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref302)
  Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- School photo of teachers. 40 x 30.4 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref303)
  Color Photography; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- The Japanese Garden in Helwan. 39.7 x 29.8 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref304)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints
- Helwan Observatory. 39.7 x 29.7 cm, 1903; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref305)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Observatory; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Students; Telescope
- Ezbet El-Walda, tombs of first and second dynasties. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref306)
  Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Arabic Writing; Archaeological Sites; Cemeteries; Egyptian clothing; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- Men cutting stones in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Circa 1900; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref307)
  Arabic Writing; Egyptian clothing; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Quarry/Mine; Rocks; Workers
- First grade school photo. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, CIrca 1890-1892; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref308)
  Boys; Egyptian clothing; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- The Japanese Garden. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref309)
  Architecture; Boys; Group Portraits; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints; Priests; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- A group of priests. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1932; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref310)
  Arabic Writing; Cars; Clothing; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses
- Helwan's hot springs. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref311)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Springs; Students; Teachers; Water; Women; Women's Clothing
- A children's nursery on Thabet Street in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1957-1958; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref312)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Photographic Prints; Windows
- A Coptic - Evangelical church in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1901; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref313)
  Architecture; Churches; Evangelical Church; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Religion; Religious Sites; Streets/Roads
- Group school photo of teachers and priests. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref314)
  Group Portraits; Head Covers; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Schools/Education; Teachers; Women
- Kiosk on Onsi Street in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref315)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Kiosk/Kushk; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Streets/Roads
- Holy Family Church. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1890; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref316)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
- Ezbet El-Walda, tombs of first and second dynasties. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref317)
  Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Arabic Writing; Archaeological Sites; Cemeteries; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Pottery; Tombs
- Monument to the Bonavia family in the Catholic cemetery in Helwan. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref318)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Cemeteries; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Sculpture; Statues; Tombs
- Jewish Cemetery in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref319)
  Architecture; Cemeteries; Helwan, Egypt; Jewish religion; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
- A view of a mosque, church and a school. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref320)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Schools/Education
- The Japanese Garden. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1948-1949; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref321)
  Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Parks; Photographic Prints; Statues; Water
- Facade of villa no. 11 on Mansour Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref322)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Greek Orthodox church on Sherif street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref323)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Orthodox Christianity; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Religious Sites; Streets/Roads
- Conversion of school building to a prison during the war in 1943 in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref324)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boys; Fences; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Military/Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Prisons; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Wars
- Villa no. 11 on Mansour Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref325)
- Villa no. 26 on Borhan Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref326)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Villa no. 33 Riad Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref327)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Villa no. 22 on Mahmud Khater Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref328)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints
- Villa Noureldin (no. 14) on Riad Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref329)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Buildings; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Windows
- People entering the Holy Family Church. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1936; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref330)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Al-Tewfik Mosque. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1884; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref331)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Islamic Architecture; Italian Writing; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
- Cimegotto family tomb in the Catholic cemetery. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1983; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref332)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Cemeteries; Death; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Tombs
- Kiosk on Ahmed Onsi Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref333)
  Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Kiosk/Kushk; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Holy Family Church beside the Holy Family School - the priest's house. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1890; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref334)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education
- Villa no. 38 on Heidar Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref335)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Lanterns/Lamps; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Women
- Villa no. 11 on Ragheb Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref336)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Boys in front of building no. 6 on Saleh Sobhi Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref337)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- A boy on Mahmud Khater Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref338)
  Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Windows
- Villa no. 38 on Heidar Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref339)
  Animals; Architecture; Buildings; Chairs; Dogs; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Statues
- Villa no. 10 on Youseph street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref340)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Kiosk/Kushk; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- A priest holding lifting up a boy. 38.1 x 27.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref341)
  Boys; Color Photography; Egyptian clothing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Studio Photography
- The Tawfiq Mosque. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1884; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref342)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Islamic Architecture; Mosques; Photographic Prints
- Boys posing beside a sphinx during an excursion to Saqqara. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref343)
  Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Boys; Children; Field-trip; Guns; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Saqqara, Egypt; Statues; Students
- A man with a little boy in front of Villa Maraghi. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref344)
  Architecture; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints
- Helwan Public Hospital, previously known as Fouad I Sanitarium. And previously Al Hyatt Hotel. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1926; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref345)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Hospitals; Hotels; Nurses; Photographic Prints; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums
- Group portrait of priests. 29.7 x 39.7 cm, 1948; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref346)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests
- Saint George Church. Previously known as the German Church. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1871; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref347)
  Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints
- Holy Family Church. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1888; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref348)
  Architecture; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Trees
- Villa no. 26 on AbdelRahman Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref349)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints; Windows
- Villa no. 36 on Mahmud Khater Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref350)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Helwan, Egypt; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees; Windows
- House no. 37 AbdelRahman street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref351)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Photographic Prints; Windows
- Entrance of house no. 23 on Mohammad Saied Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref352)
  Architecture; Doors; Entrance; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Villa no. 10 on Ibrahim Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref353)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Windows
- Villa of Mahmoud Khater. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref354)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Street lamps; Trees; Windows
- Villa on Latif Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref355)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Windows
- Al Arian Monastery in Maassara. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref356)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Monastery/Convent; Photographic Prints; Trees
- Cars in front of Princess Khadija's villa. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref357)
  Architecture; Cars; Egyptian clothing; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Royalty; Windows
- Jewish Synagogue. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1892; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref358)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Jewish religion; Photographic Prints; Synagogues; Windows
- View from East South Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref359)
  Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Trees; Windows
- View from East Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref360)
  Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Windows
- A view of Helwan from the North. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref361)
  Archigos (Database); Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Windows
- A view of Helwan's train station. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref362)
  Architecture; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Train Station/Railway Station; Windows
- The Holy Family School for Boys. 19.5 x 30 cm, 1979; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref363)
  Architecture; Buildings; Buses; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Stairs; Windows
- The Holy Family School for Boys. 30.5 x 24 cm, 1986; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref364)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Stairs; Train Station/Railway Station; Trains; Trees; Windows
- The metro station at Helwan. 19.7 x 29.5 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref365)
  Architecture; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Relationships, Interpersonal; Train Station/Railway Station; Trains
- A man shaking a boy's hand. 25.3 x 19.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref366)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Relationships, Interpersonal; Scouts; Teachers; Uniforms
- A group photo of boy scouts with their instructors. 18.3 x 30 cm, 1980/81; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref367)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Scouts; Teachers
- Students in the Holy Family School. 24 x 26.5 cm, 1980/84; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref368)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students
- Group photo of little boys with their teacher. 20.2 x 29.2 cm, 1985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref369)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Teachers
- Students at the Holy Family School. 23.8 x 30 cm, 1982; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref370)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Windows
- Two old men. 21.6 x 26.4 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref371)
  Egyptian clothing; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints
- Egyptian statues. 20.2 x 25.4 cm, 1936; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref372)
  Helwan, Egypt; History; Photographic Prints; Statues
- Boys and men at an entrance of a building. 12.8 x 26.3 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref373)
  Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Clothing; Entrance; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints
- School photo of students with their teacher and two priests. 17.7 x 23.2 cm, 1960/61; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref374)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Entrance of a villa on Ragheb Street. 24.2 x 18.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref375)
- House on AbdelRahman Street. 18.1 x 24.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref376)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Doors; Entrance; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Windows
- House on Sobhi Street with clothes held on a laundry rope on a balcony. 24.2 x 18 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref377)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Clothing; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Ropes; Windows
- The minaret of the Holy Family Church. 23.9 x 18.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref378)
  Architecture; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Religion
- Students in a marching band. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, 1952; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref379)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Flags; Helwan, Egypt; Marching band; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Students
- Funeral of Father Giacomelli. 16.5 x 24 cm, 1924; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref380)
  Architecture; Boys; Death; Funeral Proceedings; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Priests; School uniforms; Students
- Group photo of students with their teachers during a field-trip. 17.9 x 23.5 cm, 1930; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref381)
  Animals; Camels; Field-trip; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Students; Teachers
- School photo. 17 x 23.7 cm, 1956/57; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref382)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers